她指给我一段神盾局中国部的传输数据
She pointed me to a Chinese S.H.I.E.L.D. feed --
想让我破解
wanted me to crack it.
你觉得那样没有恶意吗
You thought that was harmless?
我查过数据流了
I checked the data stream.
跟我和你以前
It didn't seem like anything
放出去的信息差不多  斯凯
you and I hadn't already put out there, Skye.
我还查了给我汇款的账户
And I traced the account where the money came from
想确保不是什么邪恶的公司
to make sure it wasn't some evil corporation.
结果发现那只是个生态研究实验室
It was just an eco-research lab.
否则  我是绝不会...
Otherwise, I would never --
生态研究
Ecological research?
对  研究昆虫  蜈蚣什么的
Yeah, insects, some study with centipedes.
研究这个肯定没什么危害吧
What's more harmless than that?
好像血清里的不稳定成分被中和了
It appears the volatility in the serum has been neutralized.